Contact

dvonnegreen@live.com

www.linkedin.com/in/dvonne-morris-05513495 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Basic Life Support (BLS)

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)

Dvonne Morris

Emergency Room Registered Nurse at Imperial Point Medical Center Fort Lauderdale, Florida

Summary

Healthcare provider of 11 years, experiences ranging from home care to ER and ICU. Ability to adapt to new work environments and accept changes easily. Competence to document assessment and observations using various EMR systems. While collaborating in an interdisciplinary process, utilizing time management skills and organization to facilitate care in a patient-centered program.

Experience

Imperial Point Medical Center Emergency Room Registered Nurse July 2018 - Present (2 years 1 month)

HealthTrust Workforce Solutions
Emergency Room Registered Nurse
December 2016 - Present (3 years 8 months)
Miami/Fort Lauderdale Area

Working as an emergency room nurse within various HCA Hospitals in the Miami/Fort Lauderdale area.

Sharp HealthCare Emergency Room Registered Nurse January 2018 - April 2018 (4 months) San Diego, California

Travel assignment. 40+ bed ER Adults/Peds Acute Care

Boca Raton Regional Hospital
Training Specialist
September 2017 - December 2017 (4 months)
Boca Raton

Cerner trainer serving as the primary support contact and expert for Cerner and hospital team. Training and assisting doctors and nurses in FirstNet, Powerchart

Alameda Health System Emergency Room Registered Nurse April 2017 - August 2017 (5 months)

Oakland, California

Trauma level II, teaching hospital

Tenet Healthcare Emergency Room Registered Nurse January 2017 - March 2017 (3 months) Miami/Fort Lauderdale Area

Adult/Pediatric

Collect and plan the care of patients using the nursing model of assessment, planning, intervention, and evaluation

Provide high-quality nursing care adhering to established clinical nursing practices

Initiating community-based discharge education

Collaborate across disciplines to coordinate patient care

Huffmaster

Emergency Room Registered Nurse September 2016 - November 2016 (3 months)

Staff relief emergency room nurse

University of Miami, Miller School of Medicine Clinical Specialist July 2016 - October 2016 (4 months) Miami

Temporary staff relief
Insurance approvals/appeals
Patient telephone triage/care management
Multi-disciplinary communication and collaboration of care
Gastroenterology Clinic

Holy Cross Hospital Emergency Room RN II March 2014 - July 2016 (2 years 5 months)

Miami/Fort Lauderdale Area

Adult/Pediatric

Collect and plan the care of patients using the nursing model of assessment, planning, intervention, and evaluation

Provide high-quality nursing care adhering to established clinical nursing practices

Initiating community-based discharge education

Collaborate across disciplines to coordinate patient care

Bethesda Health

ER RN

December 2012 - December 2014 (2 years 1 month)

West Palm Beach, Florida Area

Adult/Pediatric

Collect and plan the care of patients using the nursing model of assessment, planning, intervention, and evaluation

Provide high-quality nursing care adhering to established clinical nursing practices

Initiating community-based discharge education

Collaborate across disciplines to coordinate patient care

Kendall Regional Hospital Registered Respiratory Therapist September 2010 - June 2014 (3 years 10 months)

Baptist Health South Florida Registered Respiratory Therapist June 2008 - March 2011 (2 years 10 months)

Education

Capella University

Master's degree, Informatics · (2016 - 2018)

Miami Dade College

Associate's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2010 - 2011)